<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Recipes</string>

    <string name="Tofu">Tofu</string>
    <string name="tofu">It\'s a good dish. every sadfa\nhould try.</string>
    <string name="Cofu">Cream</string>
    <string name="cofu"> a good dish. every sho\nuld try.</string>
    <string name="Dofu">Tfdfofu</string>
    <string name="dofu">ILovesh. every \n\nshould try.</string>
    <string name="Eofu">TFucking Goodu</string>
    <string name="eofu">Try sonmes a g\n\nood dish. every should try.</string>


    <string name="des_tofu">\n43 calories, 15 grams fat, 19 grams carbohydrates, 14 grams protein, 570 milligrams sodium, 4 grams fiber
\n
    In this unique recipe, slabs of tofu are immersed in a nutty mixture of pistachio and breadcrumbs for a flavor-packed dish with an interesting texture.
\n\n\n
    Ingredients:
\n
    14 oz. tofu
\n
    2 tbsp. low-sodium soy sauce
\n
    1 1/2 slices whole-wheat bread
\n
    1/2 c. pistachio nuts
\n
    Ground pepper to taste
\n
    2 tbsp. spicy mustard
\n
    2 tbsp. maple syrup
\n
    1/2 tbsp. low-sodium soy sauce
\n
    1 tbsp. tofu mayonnaise
\n
    Directions:
\n\n
        Preheat oven to 400 degrees; prepare a baking sheet by either oiling it lightly or lining it with a silicone liner. Cut the tofu into 8 1/2-in. slices and dry them lightly with paper towels. Brush both sides of the tofu with the 2 tbsp. soy sauce and set aside to marinate for at least 10 minutes. While the tofu is marinating, place the bread into the food processor and pulse into fine crumbs. Measure out 1 cup of crumbs into a wide, shallow bowl (save any remaining crumbs for another use.) Pulse the pistachios in the processor until they are reduced to fine crumbs. Add them to the breadcrumbs along with a generous grating of black pepper, and mix well. In another shallow bowl, combine the mustard, syrup, soy sauce, and mayo. Dip a slice of tofu into the mustard mixture, lightly coating all sides; then place it into the breadcrumbs, sprinkle crumbs over the top and sides, and lightly press them into the tofu. Place on the prepared baking sheet. Repeat with all slices of tofu. Put the tofu into the oven and bake for 20 minutes, or until breadcrumbs are golden brown. Serve with the sauce of your choice.</string>
    <string name="fuck">Fck it</string>
</resources>